Guide to the International Platform Association records, 1904-2001 MS2273
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1962-1995; Series 6; 14.5 Linear Feet
  - [Photographs], circa 1965-1985; Series 6 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1965-1975; Series 6 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1965-1975; Series 6 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1965-1975; Series 6 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1985-1995; Series 6 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1979; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of convention], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of convention], 1981; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - [Photographs of conventions], circa 1980-1990; Series 6 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Platform speakers, 1979; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Seaborg, Glen, 1979; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Theater, 1979; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1979; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Lakeside extra copies, circa 1962-1973; Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 1)
  - Black and white 8X10 pictures, 1966; Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 2)
  - Pictures of Victor Borge, Jack Anderson, President Lyndon Johnson, Drew Pearson, Dan Moore, 1966; Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 3)
  - Convention pictures 1-400, 1972; Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 4)
  - Convention pictures, 401-681, 1972; Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 5)
  - 8X10 Black and white, misc. no numbers, 1973-1972; Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 6)
  - Extra copies 1973 convention photos, Series 6 (Carton 53, Box 7)
  - 8X10 Black and white pictures nos. 601-835, 1977; Series 6 (Carton 54, Box 1)
  - 8X10 Black and white pictures nos. 401-600, 1977; Series 6 (Carton 54, Box 2)
  - 1978, Series 6 (Carton 54, Box 3)
  - 8X10 Black and white pictures, 1982; Series 6 (Carton 54, Box 4)
  - 8X10 Black and white pictures, 1985; Series 6 (Carton 54, Box 5)
  - 8X10 Black and white pictures plus 3X5 colored pictures, 1987; Series 6 (Carton 54, Box 6)
  - [Convention photographs], 1967-1968; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 1)
  - The Lakeside years, circa 1967-1968; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 2)
  - [Convention photographs], 1973; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 3)
  - [Convention photographs], 1974; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 4)
  - [Convention photographs], 1975; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 5)
  - [Convention photographs], 1976; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 6)
  - [Convention photographs], 1977; Series 6 (Box 55, Binder 7)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Binder 1)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1970-1980; Series 6 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Box 1, 1973; Series 6 (Carton 57)
  - Box 2, 1973; Series 6 (Carton 57)
  - Box 3, 1973; Series 6 (Carton 57)
  - Box 4, 1974; Series 6 (Carton 57)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures no 1 thru 500, 1974; Series 6 (Carton 57, Box 5)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures no. 501 thru 1201, 1974; Series 6 (Carton 57, Box 6)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures no. 1 thru no. 400, 1975; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 1)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures 401 thru 900, 1975; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 2)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures no. 1-450, 1976; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 3)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures nos. 451-850, 1976; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 4)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures nos. 851-1224, 1976; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 5)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures nos. 0-200, 1977; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 6)
  - 8X10 black and white pictures nos. 201-400, 1977; Series 6 (Carton 58, Box 7)
- Audiovisual materials, 1977-1999; 1990-1999; Series 7; 23 Linear Feet
  Arranged into audio and visual categories, and arranged chronologically within each category.
  This series contains both audiotapes and videotapes documenting annual conferences of the International Platform Association between 1977 and 1999.
  - 1977 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 1)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes containing speeches delivered by Lawrence Kraus, Harold Russell, James Schlesinger, Franz Allers, Henri St. Laurent, Hal Holbrook, Billy Ray Cox, T.T. Toppen, John Rothman, Fletcher Byrom, John Currie, Norman Lear, Jean Harris, Ron Nessen, Ernst Wittenberg, Suzy Mallery, and Jeane Nixon. It also contains recordings of a nuclear energy debate and the Young American Oratorial.
  - 1977 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 2)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes that contain speeches delivered by Lowell Thomas, Barbara Walters, Ralph Nader, Jack Anderson, Ross Hersey, Norman Rebin, John Henry Faulk, James Schlesinger, Grayson Lynch, Charles Jarvis, Richard Scammon, Donald Sarbacker, James Kilpatrick, Rudy Vallee, Bert Lance, and Dale Smith.
  - 1977-1978 Convention, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 3)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes of speeches delivered by John Currie, John Henry Faulk, Ross Hersey, George Crile, Jean Harris, Charles Jarvis, Frank Abagnale, Joseph A. Califano, Jr., Franz Allers, Fletcher Byron, and Jeane Nixon.
  - 1978 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 4)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes of speeches delivered by Jack Anderson, Domenico Facci, Seymour Hersh, Abner Mikva, Henry Jackson, Victor Vertes, Justin Dart-Eaton, Sheila Tobias, Joseph Sugarman, and Patricia Schroeder.
  - 1978 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 5)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes of speeches delivered by Rudy Maxa, Hal Holbrook, Edward Elson, James Kilpatrick, Joel Kurtzman, Lawrence Kraus, and Bert Lance. It also contains recordings of a meeting management seminar.
  - 1978 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 6)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes featuring speeches by Norman Lear, Seymour Hersh, Herbert Glieberman, Cleo Dawson, Ruth Glick, Sandy LinverGrayton Lynch, Rod McKuen, Louis Villanova, Suzy Mallery, Ralph Nader, and Ron Nessen.
  - 1978 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 7)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Douglas Pike, Benjamin Ruhe, Charles Trentham, William Proxmire, Ernest Wittenberg, William Safire, John Singlaub, Henri St. Lawrant, James Schlesigner, Ilene Savin, Harold Russell, and Richard Scammon.
  - 1978 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 8)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes containing speeches delivered by Rudy Vallee, George Crile, Joseph Sugarman, Patricia Schroeder, Sheila Tobias, Jack Anderson, Edward Elson, Frank Abagnale, Victor Vertes, Abner Mikva, and Hal Holbrook.
  - 1978 Convention VI, Series 7 (Box 59, Case 9)
    This case contains eight audiotapes featuring speeches made by Justin Dart, Jeane Dixon, Leon Jaworski, Rudy Maxa, and Henry Jackson.
  - 1979 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 60, Case 1)
    This case contains twelve audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Ralph Nader, Arthur B. Laffer, George Crile III, Henry J. Heimlich, Dennis Kucinich, Thomas Bagley-White, Horace E. Dobbs, E. Mandell de Windt, Malcolm S. Forbes, Alexander Haiy, Hyman Rickover, and Jeane Dixon.
  - 1979 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 60, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Phillip M. Crane, Isaac Asimov, Glenn Seaborg, James Kilpatrick, Jesse Helms, Howard J. Ruff, Joseph Sugarman, Jamie L. Whitten, and Robert Leiman.
  - 1979 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 60, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Michael Debakey, Rosemary L. Ginn, Jack Anderson, Sheikh Salaam, Shirley Duncan, Isaac Asimov, Hal Holbrook, Phillip Crane, and James Kilpatrick.
  - 1979 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 60, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by William Meredith, Joseph Sugarman, Helgg Sandberg, Jesse Helms, Rosemary Ginn, Thomas Bagley White, James Kilpatrick, Henry Heimlich, Hyman Rickover, Michael DeBakey, and Sheikh Salaam.
  - 1979 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 60, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jack Anderson, E. Mandell DeWindt, Malcolm Forbes, Robert Leiman, Shirley Duncan, and James L. Whitten.
  - 1979 Convention VI, Series 7 (Box 60, Case 6)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Hal Holbrook, Dennis Kucinich, Ralph Nader, Horace Dobbs, Glenn Seaborg, Alexander Haig, Howard Ruff, and Jeane Dixon.
  - 1980 I, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by William Sullivan, Chris Gugas, Jack Anderson, Ryan Frank Vogl, Robert C Byrd, Henry Heimoich, and Harry Blackstone.
  - 1980 II, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by John DeSalvo, Billy Mills, Lonny Rogers, Morris Barr, Glenn T. Seaborg, Walter Sullivan, and Mark Russell.
  - 1980 III, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by John Ciardi, Richard Schibert, Billy Mills, James Hall, Gary Couture, Herbert Meyers, Pamela Moore-Epstein, Juanita Kreps, Strom Thurmond, William Chambliss, and Joe Girard.
  - 1980 IV, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 4)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Joseph Sugarman.
  - 1980 V, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 5)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jeane Dixon, Ralph Nader, John Pickerell, and G. Gordon Liddy.
  - 1980 VI, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 6)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered byRichard Lesher, Redd Larson, Paul Pickel, William Sauber, Phillip L. McHugh, Brother Blue, Stanley Arnold, Elizabeth Charlton-Moore, Betty Southard-Murphy, and Carolyn Warner.
  - 1980 VII, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 7)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Jack Anderson, Morris Barr, Robert C. Byrd, Stanley Arnold, Harry Blackstone, William Chambliss, John Clardi, Jeane Dixon, Chris Gugas, John DeSalvo, Joe Girard, and James Hall.
  - 1980 VIII, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 8)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Lloyd N. Cutler, Bob Woodward, Richard Lugar, Abba Eban, Howard Baker, George Sheehan, Jim McKay, and Charles Kuralt.
  - 1980 IX, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 9)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Robert J. Ryan, Joseph Sugarman, Carey Connell-Sutton, Mark Russell, Richard Schubert, Frank Vogel, William Sullivan, Carolyn Warner, and Strom Thurmond.
  - 1980 X, Series 7 (Box 61, Case 10)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Henry Heimlich, Arthur Laffer, Richard Lesher, Juanita Kreps, Reed Larson, G. Gordon Liddy, Herbert E. Meyers, Hugh Morgan Hill, John Pickerell, Pamela Moore-Epstein, Ralph Nader, and Lonny Rodgers.
  - 1981 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 62, Case 1)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Dan Moore, R.H. Kauffman, F. Lee Bailey, Harry Hurwitz, Gale McGee, Leo Cherne, Tom Caldwell, Martin Galvin, William Windom, Richard Berendzen, Stuart Eizenhart, Christopher VanHoller, Donald Johanson, Michael Beschloss, Jeane Dixon, Peter James, Robert White, and Ralph Nader.
  - 1981 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 62, Case 2)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by James Kilpatrick, Bruce Laingen, Herbert Scriner, Lowell Thomas, David Brinkley, Jack Anderson, Susan King, and Herman Wouk.
  - 1981 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 62, Case 3)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Sheila Tate, Malcolm S. Forbes, Jr., Dick Cavett, Henry Heimlich, H. Roy Kaplan, Herbert J. Stern, Jeff Greenfield, and Teddy Pendergrass.
  - 1981 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 62, Case 4)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Peter N. James, Robert White, Arnaud De Borchgrave, Ralph Nader, Christopher Van Hollen, Donald C. Johanson, James Kilpatrick, David Stockman, Venita Van Capsel, Bruce Laingen, Herbert Striner, Susan King, and Herman Wouk.
  - 1981 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 62, Case 5)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by F. Lee Bailey, Gale W. McGee, Harry Hurwitz, Richard Berendzen, Stuart Eizenstat, Leo Cherne, Tom Caldwell, Martin Galvin, William Windom, Michael Beschloss, and Jeane Dixon.
  - 1981 Convention VI, Series 7 (Box 62, Case 6)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Lowell Thomas, David Brinkley, Jack Anderson, and David Sadd.
  - 1982 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 63, Case 1)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Endre Balogh, Alejandro Orfila, John Lee, Arkady Shevchenko, W.T. Toney, Jr., Donald T. Regan, Betty Beale, Bonnie Gordon Flickinger, Jack Kilpatrick, Edwin Newman, and Yeshio Okawara.
  - 1982 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 63, Case 2)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Liv Ullman, James Mork, Jack Valenti, John Denver, Richard Berendzen, Robert Komer, James C. Humes, and Judith Edwards.
  - 1982 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 63, Case 3)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by David Kline, Joe Durbin, Carole Mosbacher, Richard Valeriani, George Plimpton, Robert L. Montgomery, Frank X. Loconto, Glenn Seaborg, Dennis Flanagan, Harold Krents, Bob Boyd, Karry Blackstone, Jr., Doug Henning, Robert F. Delaney, and Fred Hayward.
  - 1982 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 63, Case 4)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by John P. Richardson, Kitty Kelley, Ralph Nader, Jack Anderson, and Art Holst.
  - 1982 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 63, Case 5)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Jeane Dixon, Claude Pepper, Wendy Lazar, Malcolm S. Forbes, Jr., J.W. Marriott, Jr., Henry Heimlich, Lowell Thomas, John Svahn, Robert Dole, Stansfield Turner, and William Ball.
  - 1983 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 1)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Mark Shields, Diana McClellan, James Lipscomb, Richard Oberlin, Marie Shepherd, Allan J. Lichtman, Judy Ryan, Malcolm S. Forbes, Jr., James D. Robinson, Marvin Cetron, Lois Fahs Timmins, Neil R. Pierce, David Wise, and P.J. O'Rourke.
  - 1983 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 2)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by G. Gordon Liddy, Ralph Nader, William Rusher, Bill Alexander, Patrick J. Buchanan, Barber Conable, William Webster, Sam Donaldson, and Larry King.
  - 1983 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 3)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Julian Bond, William F. Buckley, Jr., George Wallace, Bernie Yoh, Jim Mork, William Bolger, Joseph M. Beggs, Glenn Seaborg, and Ralph Nader.
  - 1983 Convention IV, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 4)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by John McLaughlin, Eleanor Smeal, Shirley Duncan, Jack Anderson, and Del Russo.
  - 1983 Convention V, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 5)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Julian Bond, William F. Buckley, Jr., George Wallace, June Karger, Bernie Yoh, Jim Mork, William F. Bolber, Glenn Seaborg, and Joseph Beggs.
  - 1983 Convention VI, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 6)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by G. Gordon Liddy, William Rusher, Bill Alexander, Patrick Buchanan, Barber Conable, William Webster, and Sam Donaldson.
  - 1983 Convention VII, Series 7 (Box 64, Case 7)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by King Rechad, Enrique Tejera Paris, Seymour Hersh, James Boren, Richard Henning, Harry Blackstone, Jim Bostain, Thomas Slavens, and Joe Glazer.
  - [1983 Convention], Series 7 (Box 64, Case 8)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Robert Leiman, Sheikh Ibn Ben Salam, Ruth Warrick, Gretchen Chellson, Ralph Nader, Bess Abell, Henry Heimlich, John Mutz, Barry Reed, John Nicola, and George Crile.
  - [1983 Convention], Series 7 (Box 64, Case 9)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by John McCaughlin, Eleanor Smeal, Shirley Duncan, Jack Anderson, Del Russo, and Victor Borge.
  - [1983 Convention], Series 7 (Box 64, Case 10)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Floyd Riddick, Minnie Pearl, Mario Cuomo, James Filpatrick, J. Peter Grace, Jesse Jackson, Leon Martel, E. Larry Moles, Bernard Shaw, Malcolm Forbes, Jr., Charles Wohlstetter.
  - [1983 Convention], Series 7 (Box 64, Case 11)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Hal Bruno, Carlton Sedgeley, Betty Williams, Harry Blackstone, Ricky Jay, Mary S. Calderone, Nikki Nyetski, Edwin Baron, Minerva Braden-Black, Mary Cunningham, Merelyn Reeve, and Frank Cappiello.
  - 1984 Convention 011-110, Series 7 (Box 65, Case 1)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Robert Leiman, Sheikh Ibn Ben Salaam, Ruth Warrick, Ralph Nader, Bess Abell, Henry Heimlich, John Mutz, Barry Reed, John Nicola, and George Crile.
  - 1984 Convention 120-230, Series 7 (Box 65, Case 2)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Hal Bruno, Carlton Sedgeley, Betty Williams, Harry Blackstone, Ricky Jay, Mary Calderone, Nikki Nyetski, Edwin Baron, Minerva Braden-Black, Mary Cunningham, Merelyn Reeve, and Frank Cappiello.
  - 1984 Convention 240-360, Series 7 (Box 65, Case 3)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Floyd Roderick, Minnie Pearl, Murray Banks, James Kilpatrick, J. Peter Grace, Malcolm Forbes, Jr., Charles Wohlsetter, E. Larry Moles, Bernard Shaw, Mario Cuomo, Gene Perret, Jesse Jackson, and Leon Martel.
  - 1984 Convention 370-470, Series 7 (Box 65, Case 4)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by David Best, Robert Leiman, Ned Dobner, Jean-Michel Cousteau, Thomas Hudgens, Jerry Teplitz, Peter Lance, Vladimir Sakharov, Michael Morgenstern, Jack Anderson, Joseph Schwartz, and Allan Lichtman.
  - 1985 Convention 011-100, Series 7 (Box 66, Case 1)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Bob Leiman, Dan Moore, Linda Clauder, Frant Wright, William Colby, Sally Shelton Colby, Harry Blackstone, Jr., Evan Galbraith, Jerry Parr, Steve Allen, Jr., Richard Ittner, and Joan Mondale.
  - 1985 Convention 120-240, Series 7 (Box 66, Case 2)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Larry King, Jack Anderson, Clause Pepper, Stansfield Turner, Brooke Knapp, J. Peter Grace, Vicki Valentine, Sunny Schlenger, Shirley Chisholm, Wayne F. Nelson, John McLaughlin, Robert Dole.
  - 1985 Convention 250-340, Series 7 (Box 66, Case 3)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Sheila Tate, Malcolm S. Forbes, Jr., Dick Cavett, Henry Heimlich, Roy Kaplan, Jeff Greenfield, and Herbert Stern.
  - 1985 Convention 350-440, Series 7 (Box 66, Case 4)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Teddy Pendergrass, Shere Hite, Edythe Bregnard, Lloyd Owens, Shirley Duncan, Richard Berendzen, Mary McBride, Jack Anderson, and Jeane Dixon.
  - 1985 Convention 370-440, Series 7 (Box 66, Case 5)
    This case contains audiocassettes featuring speeches made by Shere Hite, Richard Berendzen, Lloyd Owens, Shirley Duncan, and Jack Anderson.
  - 1986 Convention 400-490, Series 7 (Box 67, Case 1)
  - 1986 Conventions 500-510, Series 7 (Box 67, Case 2)
  - 1988 Convention, Series 7 (Box 67, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Murray Banks, Gerry Tausch, Charles Inlander, Bill McLinn, Bill PLante, John Carter Brown, Joe Clark, Edwin Meese, Bill Schustik, Archibald Roosevelt, Malcolm Forbes, Jr., John Roach, and Roger McFarlane.
  - 1988 Convention VII, 51-370 (incomplete), Series 7 (Box 67, Case 4)
  - 1986 Convention 010-140, Series 7 (Box 68, Case 1)
  - 1986 Convention 140-240, Series 7 (Box 68, Case 2)
  - 1986 Convention 250-390, Series 7 (Box 68, Case 3)
  - 1987 Convention I, Series 7 (Box 69, Case 1)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by George Crile, Dale Van Atta, Clayton Yeutter, and Bob Levy-Washington.
  - 1987 Convention II, Series 7 (Box 69, Case 2)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Bettina Gregory, Albert Blaustein, Cornelius W. Heine, Gordon Liddy, Adolpho Calero, Peter Kostmayer, Rodger McFarlane, Bill Schustik, Andrea Mitchell, and Sydney Biddle Barrows.
  - 1987 Convention III, Series 7 (Box 69, Case 3)
    This case contains audiotapes featuring speeches delivered by Remar Sutton, Douglas Lamont, Ted Turner, James Humes, Henry Heimlich, Rand Araskog, Sam Donaldson, Jeremy Rifkin, and Dietrick Thomsen.